# **Petro Bazurin**

## Senior FE developer

07391 645187
<a href="mailto:petr.bazurin@gmail.com">petr.bazurin@gmail.com</a>
Maldon, UK
Ukrainian (3 years work permit visa)

www.linkedin.com/in/petr-bazurin-3a52b635 github.com/pbazurin

10+ years of experience working in information technologies as a FE developer, 6+ years of experience with Angular 2+.

Since 2018, worked on a global E-commerce solution as a senior FE developer in a big international company. Earlier was leading the development of a cloud based web portal for managing of data backup / recovery products as a part of big SaaS solution.

## **SKILLS**

Angular, RxJs, NgRx, Nx, MFE, Node.js, NestJS, Azure, ADO, .NET C#

## **EXPERIENCE**

## Senior FE developer

Polytech software / ESW (outstaffing, Ukraine)

September 2018 – Present

ESW is a Dublin company that facilitates the e-commerce strategy of some of the world's biggest brands like Nike and Victoria Secrets.

- Led / guided UI developers to work on the checkout web application
- Developed solutions for analytics, A/B testing, brand styling, visual testing
- Assisted with technology evolution from shared packages to MFE and web-components

Angular 6-13, RxJs, NgRx, Jasmine / Karma, Protractor, Playwright, Nx, MFE, Stencil.js, Azure, ADO

#### **FE Team Lead**

Softheme / Quest (outsourcing, Ukraine)

April 2016 – August 2018

Quest QorePortal – a cloud-based portal for monitoring and managing of data protection solutions.

- · Led a team of 6 engineers handling end-to-end development of QorePortal
- Guided the adoption of the Angular framework
- Participated in "on-premise to cloud" infrastructure migration

Angular 2-6, RxJs, Jasmine / Karma, Protractor, .NET C#, Web API 2, Azure Service Fabric, Canvas

## Senior FE developer

Softheme / Dell (outsourcing, Ukraine)

February 2012 – April 2016

AppAssure / Dell Rapid Recovery — an on-premise application designed to simplify backup and recovery for enterprise clients for systems, applications, and data protection.

- Developed a "wizard" solution that replaced complex user setups / flow
- Worked on bug fixing, web performance improvements, tech solution changes

.Net 4.0, C#, ASP.NET MVC 4, NUnit, DevExpress, PokeIn, JavaScript, AJAX, jQuery

#### **EDUCATION**

MS in Information Systems and Technologies

September 2006 – May 2012

NTUU KPI, Kyiv, Ukraine